Hello, my name is [inaudible] and I'll be
مرحبًا، اسمي [inaudible] وسأكون كذلك
your instructor for this course on managing freelancing projects.
مدرسك في هذه الدورة التدريبية حول إدارة المشاريع الحرة.
I run a software startup,
أدير شركة ناشئة،
which is a social enterprise where we crunch a lot of data about
وهي مؤسسة اجتماعية حيث نعالج الكثير من البيانات المتعلقة
social impact and projects for the underprivileged communities in India.
بالأثر الاجتماعي والمشاريع للمجتمعات المحرومة في الهند.
I started my freelancing journey about five years ago when I was just
بدأت رحلتي في العمل الحر منذ حوالي خمس سنوات عندما
launching my startup since I needed money on the site to sustain my company.
أطلقت شركتي الناشئة لأنني كنت بحاجة إلى المال على الموقع للحفاظ على شركتي.
We have also hired freelancers to work for our startup in various roles.
لقد قمنا أيضًا بتعيين موظفي العمل الحر للعمل في شركتنا الناشئة في مناصب مختلفة.
I take a lot of decisions,
أتخذ الكثير من القرارات،
even big decisions with my heart and not much with mind,
حتى القرارات الكبيرة بقلبي وليس الكثير من التفكير،
and I realized that the power of our intuition can
وأدركت أن قوة حدسنا يمكنها ذلك
take us really far in the personal and professional world.
تأخذنا بعيدًا حقًا في العالم الشخصي والمهني.
I've worked with 90 plus clients from all over
لقد عملت مع أكثر من 90 عميلًا من جميع أنحاء العالم
the world and have had amazing learnings from this freelancing journey,
وتعلمت بشكل مذهل من رحلة العمل الحر هذه،
which has enabled me to not only run my startup but also be
مما مكنني ليس فقط من تشغيل شركة ناشئة خاصة بي، ولكن أيضًا
able to hire freelancers and help their livelihoods.
القدرة على توظيف مترجمين مستقلين ومساعدتهم على إيجاد عمل.
I'm a practitioner of heartfulness meditation and provide
أنا ممارس تأمل وأقدم
free meditations to anyone who is willing to explore meditation.
تأملات مجانية لأي شخص يرغب في استكشاف التأمل.
I'd say, get used to my face because you are stuck with me for the rest of the course.
أود أن أقول، تعتاد على وجهي لأنك عالق معي لبقية الدورة.